Guide to the Robert Trent Jones papers, ca. 1924-2003.
Jones, Robert Trent papers
- Series VI. Drawings and Plans
  - Rolled Plans
    - Miscellaneous
      - National Parks, 476
      - Playa Dorada painting, 481
      - Posters, 479, 478, 482, 483
      - Pump systems, 482
      - Purchase, 438
      - RTJ Homes, 480
      - Scholz Homes, 475
      - Snowmobile track, 482
      - Unidentified plans, 485, 486, 487, 488
      - White Golf Course, 473